E

LATUANJA CARSON

Maryland Heights, Missouri □ (314)517-1441 □

latuanja.c@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/latuanja-carson GitHub: https://github.com/latuanja

Portfolio: https://latuanja.github.io/LCarson_Professional_Portfolio

PROJECT MANAGEMENT | OFFICE MANNAGEMENT | COMMUNICATIONS

Experienced self-starter that thrives in a fast paced environment and remains intellectually curious while managing specialized projects and communicating professionally and effectively with both internal and external partners.

CORE STRENGTHS

- Office Management
- Scheduling & Travel
- Project Management
- Detail Oriented
- Payroll & Expense Reports
- Order Fulfillment
- Customer Service
- Strategic Thinker
- Audio Visual & Presentations
- Inventory Control & Purchasing
- Quick Books & Book-Keeping
- Strong Microsoft & Computer Skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

INTOXIMETERS, INC. -ST. LOUIS, MO.

2013 - Present

Specializing in B2B services which includes the design, manufacturing and selling of breath alcohol testing products for screening and evidential applications worldwide.

INTERIM TECHNICAL SUPERVISOR (MAY 2018- PRESENT)

Supervising and managing the daily operations of the Technical Department to meet corporate objectives while developing & executing initiatives that meet the needs of all stakeholders.

- Daily collaboration with Technical Director and Department Manager regarding team projects & status updates
- Cross-functional teaming with internal management partners to mitigate servicing risk
- Plans, coordinates and supervise the daily functions of personnel while mentoring and providing expert technical assistance as merited
- Monitor and react to established performance indicators, including: budget variances, production, quality and safety metrics
- Compose departmental SOP and ensure staff comprehension upon hire and during daily workflow
- Manage specialized projects as assigned by Director for inventory control and general servicing
- Negotiate servicing contracts with optimal cost-savings terms for customer and organization

TECHNICAL ADMINISTRATOR (2013- PRESENT)

Performs various administrative duties associated with the daily operations of the Technical Department for Intoximeters while also conducting interim-supervisory functions.

- Supports general business operations through the completion of administrative task such as preparation and editing of presentations, proposals and correspondence.
- Schedule service repairs and certifications
- Ensures that communication channels are established and used for all internal & external
- Perform monthly cycle counts, weekly audits, and biannual full scope physical inventory
- Actively manage instrument conversions for purchase orders and additional quality control task

FOUR WINDS IN-HOME HEALTH CARE, LLC. - MARYLAND HEIGHTS, MO

2012 - Present

 $Senior\ Home\ Care\ agency\ providing\ adult\ services\ to\ communities\ within\ the\ St.\ Louis\ area.$

OFFICE MANAGER

Achieve revenue goals by effectively managing client scheduling, staff productivity, collections, specialty referral process, expenses, auxiliary supply purchases while ensuring company compliance with Missouri Department of Health & Senior Services.

- Oversee all hiring, training, scheduling, payroll and any personnel servicing issues
- Initiated use of HR tracking database for efficiency in client services and time keeping/reconciliation
- Manage travel accommodations and actively communicate with medical partners regarding client services
- Management of all operational functions, general accounting payables/receivables using Quick Books.

IMPACT - ST. LOUIS, MO

2011-20

Non-profit organization specializing in supplemental programs designed for inner city schools for youth intellectual development and socio-economic empowerment.

PROGRAM MANAGER

Ensured that all training and development actives were strategically linked to the organization's mission/vision

- Managed and created contractual agreements, budgets and invoices in coherence with grant requirements
- Facilitated community outreach programs and collaborations to expand IMPACT service reach
- Institued suitable audit processes to track efficacy of training and teacher-student dynamics
- Delivered training by utilizing various learning methods across behavioral, soft skills & brand standards

CATHEDRAL OF Y'SHUA WORSHIP CENTER - EAST ST. LOUIS, MO

2007-2010

Non-profit organization catering to the spiritual needs of parishners and the surrounding communities.

DIRECTOR OF ADMINISTRATION

The Director of Administration supports the Cathedral of Y'shua Worship Center in strategic planning, implementation, administration, and promotion of ministry projects/initiatives.

- Managed all aspects of operations, budgets, and payroll while actively using QuickBooks expertise
- Ensured a robust marketing strategy for general church activities and specialized youth programs
- Formulated reports that inform staff and key stakeholders on project developments and outcoms
- Developed reporting mechanism to inform and engage individual and group constituents accordingly
- Created quality improvement mechanisms that help assess, monitor and measure projects developments and outcomes.

BARNES-JEWISH HOSPITAL - ST. LOUIS, MO

2003-2008

Major hospital / medical center servicing St. Louis Missouri with health care needs.

CLINICAL ASSISTANT

Functioned as a member of the patient care team and medical assistant as directed by medical management.

- Performed both technical and clerical task in addition to patient care functions when merited
- All duties required to complete patient check-in/check-out, administered and coordinated the HMO referral and service authorization process while performing other clinic front desk activities
- Actively communicated with patients and staff with keen awareness of general medical terminology
- Assisted Physicians with collecting necessary X-Rays, films and also transporting patients for exams

EDUCATION

WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY CODING BOOTCAMP (OCTOBER 2020 - APRIL 2021)

JAMES MCKELVEY SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING AT WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY STUDYING FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT, COVERING THE FOLLOWIGN AREAS:

- HTML
- CSS,
- JAVASCRIPT,
- JQUERY
- API's,
- BOOTSTRAP
- RESPONSIVE DESIGN
- Datastructures
- LOCAL STORAGE, SESSION STORAGE
- Algorithms
- Deployment

PROGRAM MANAGER - CERTIFICATION

Missouri Department of Health & Senior Services - Jefferson City, MO (2010)

BUSINESS & ACCOUNTING COURSES

Washington University- St. Louis, MO (2007) St. Louis Community College – St. Louis, MO (2004-2006, 2016)

> Computer Network Administration - Certification North County Technical School (2003) Hazelwood High School- Hazelwood MO (2003)

ACTIVITIES AND INTEREST

Freelance Photography/ Videography, LC Media St. Louis, MO (2016- Present)